<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meine Lieblingsrezepte</string>

    <string name="pizza_1_title">Pizza mit karamellisierten Zwiebeln und Ziegenkäse</string>
    <string name="pizza_1_description">Machen Sie eine vegetarische Pizza, die gesund und fettarm ist, anstatt einen Imbiss zu bestellen.
         Dieses einfache Rezept verwendet Ziegenkäse für den Geschmack, während die Zwiebeln ihm Süße verleihen…</string>

    <string name="pizza_2_title">BBQ chicken pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_2_description">Make a healthy, low-calorie pizza that adds up to three of your 5-a-day
        and give the takeaway a miss. The barbecue chicken lends a moreish smoky flavour</string>

    <string name="pizza_3_title">Cajun prawn pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_3_description">Make a healthy, low-fat pizza with juicy, spiced prawns instead of calling the takeaway.
        Top with peppery rocket to make it even more nutritious and delicious</string>

    <string name="pizza_4_title">Chicken tikka masala pizzas</string>
    <string name="pizza_4_description">Rustle up our spiced chicken pizzas using naan bread in just 20 minutes.
        To balance the heat, serve them with dollops of mango chutney and natural yogurt</string>

    <string name="pizza_5_title">Rainbow pizzas</string>
    <string name="pizza_5_description">Forget takeaway pizzas, encourage kids to eat a rainbow every day
        with this colourful recipe full of fresh flavours – guaranteed to please even fussy eaters…</string>

    <string name="pizza_6_title">Pork, gorgonzola &amp; garlic butter pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_6_description">Garlic butter, salty blue cheese, peppery rocket and a kick of chilli
        – these pizzas are loaded with flavour. Try making them for an indulgent weekend dinner…</string>

    <string name="pizza_7_title">Spinach &amp; blue cheese pizza</string>
    <string name="pizza_7_description">This vegetarian pizza is super-quick to make because the base is yeast free.
        Packed with spinach, walnuts, mushrooms and blue cheese, it\'s super-tasty too…</string>

    <string name="pizza_8_title">Pizza Margherita in 4 easy steps</string>
    <string name="pizza_8_description">Even a novice cook can master the art of pizza with our simple step-by-step guide.</string>

    <string name="pizza_9_title">Spelt pizza bianco with Jersey Royals</string>
    <string name="pizza_9_description">Spelt has a wonderful nutty flavour that works particularly well for pizza.
        This is a twist on classic comfort food, with Jersey Royal potatoes and herbs</string>

    <string name="pizza_10_title">Frying pan pizza with aubergine, ricotta &amp; mint</string>
    <string name="pizza_10_description">This recipe ensures a crispy-bottomed pizza without ever turning on the oven.
        It\'s easy, veggie and 2 of your 5-a-day…</string>
</resources>